<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Haozhe Su</title>
    <link>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Haozhe Su</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Fourier Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/non_fourier_diffusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/non_fourier_diffusion/</guid>
      <description>Abstract We introduce a generalized constitutive model for diffusion-driven problems with several attractive properties:
 It fundamentally explains diffusion from the perspective of the Boltzmann Transport Equation It can address the issue of infinite propagation speed for diffusion, an assumption made by the widely employed Fick’s/Fourier’s law. It can capture some of the most characteristic, yet unprecedented, visual aspects of diffusion-driven physics.  In the algorithm, we propose a novel semi-implicit discretization for this diffusion model on staggered MACgrids and design a geometric Multigrid-preconditioned Conjugate Gradients solver for efficient numerical solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Newtonian Flow</title>
      <link>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/non_newtonian_flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/non_newtonian_flow/</guid>
      <description>TO BE CONTINUED
Examples </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Us</title>
      <link>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/this_is_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/this_is_us/</guid>
      <description>This is my personal project which records beautiful moments with family and friends.
  Me and my college friends on a winder break trip to Boston Date: Dec. 31, 2018      My parents seeing me off @ Xiamen Gaoqi International Airport Date: Aug. 20, 2018      Me and my college friends on a graduation vacation to Huangshan Mountain Date: Jun. 18, 2018      Me in academic dress with my grandma and granpa (TBC) Date: Aug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2D Interactive Smoke</title>
      <link>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/smoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/smoke/</guid>
      <description>Smoke simulation is one of the most fundamental parts in physics-based simulation. In this project, we visualize 2D smoke based on 2D Navier-Stokes equation. It is composed of the following steps:
 First of all, we apply numerical methods and solve Navier-Stokes equation by splitting the original equation into three major parts:  Advection: $\frac{Dq}{dt} = 0$
Through advection, the properties of smoke move along with the velocity field Diffusion: $\frac{\partial\vec{u}}{\partial t} = \nu\nabla^2\vec{u}$</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blender Modeling</title>
      <link>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/educational/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/educational/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  The long-term goal for this project is to provide a simple and straightforward view of some basic concepts and structures in mathematics, physics, engineering and even music. We use Blender, an open-source and powerful tool to create scientific models and take advantage of its built-in Cycles renderer to make every scene cool and vivid.
 Möbius Strip   The Möbius strip or Möbius band, is a surface with only one side (when embedded in three-dimensional Euclidean space) and only one boundary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maya Modeling</title>
      <link>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/3danse_cp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/3danse_cp/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  This project is for course 3D Animation and Special Effects.
 Bear-Claw Knife   Elevator  See below for how it works:
 Motorola Cell Phone  Perspective view: Top view: Bottom view:  Tornado </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rigid Body Simulation</title>
      <link>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/rbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SoldierDown.github.io/projects/rbs/</guid>
      <description>This project is for CS523 Computer Graphics.
In this project, basic physical laws are implemented. The rigid solid cube will undergo movements, rotations, as well as collisions. The following steps are included:
 Implement the unconstraint movements of a given rigid body. Use ODE to update properties like location, velocity, angular momentum, etc. Take collisions into account and disallow inter-penetration. Typical result is shown below:
  Report
Demo</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>